Francis D. Donovan Papers
© 2011 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Photographic materials, undated, 1829-1997
  - Subseries A: Prints, undated, 1829-1997
    - Sub-subseries 1: Stations, undated, 1858-1997
      - Baldwin, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 482)
      - Baldwinville, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, circa 1964 (Box 5:, Folder 483)
      - Baldwinville, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 484)
      - Barnstable, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 485)
      - Barre, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 486)
      - Barre, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 487)
      - Barre, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 488)
      - Barre Plains, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 489)
      - Barre Plains, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1965 (Box 5:, Folder 490)
      - Barre Plains, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1965 (Box 5:, Folder 491)
      - Barre Plains, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 492)
      - Barre Plains, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 493)
      - Barre Plains, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 494)
      - Barretts Junction, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 495)
      - Barretts Junction, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 496)
      - Barrowsville, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1926 (Box 5:, Folder 497)
      - Bass River, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 498)
      - Battery, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1920 (Box 5:, Folder 499)
      - Bayside, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 500)
      - Beach Bluff, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 501)
      - Beaconfield, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 502)
      - Bearcroft, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 503)
      - Beaver Brook, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 504)
      - Beckett, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 505)
      - Bedford, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 5:, Folder 506)
      - Bedford, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 5:, Folder 507)
      - Bedford, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 5:, Folder 508)
      - Bedford Springs, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 509)
      - Bellevue, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 5:, Folder 510)
      - Bellingham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1929 (Box 5:, Folder 511)
      - Bell Rock, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 5:, Folder 512)
      - Berkshire, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 6:, Folder 513)
      - Berkshire, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 6:, Folder 514)
      - Berkshire, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 6:, Folder 515)
      - Berlin, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 516)
      - Beverley, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1963 (Box 6:, Folder 517)
      - Billerica, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 518)
      - Billerica, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, circa 1940 (Box 6:, Folder 519)
      - Billerica, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 520)
      - Bird's Hill, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 521)
      - Bleachery, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 522)
      - Bleachery, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 523)
      - Black Rock, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 6:, Folder 524)
      - Blackstone, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1961 (Box 6:, Folder 525)
      - Blackstone, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1961 (Box 6:, Folder 526)
      - Blackstone, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1961 (Box 6:, Folder 527)
      - Bondsville, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 528)
      - Bondsville, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 529)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 530)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 531)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, 1835 (Box 6:, Folder 532)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 533)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 534)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 535)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 536)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 537)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 538)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 539)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 540)
      - Boston (North Station), Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 541)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New York & New England Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 542)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1915 (Box 6:, Folder 543)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1892 (Box 6:, Folder 544)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 545)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad Station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 546)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 547)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 548)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 549)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 550)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 551)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 552)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 553)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 554)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 555)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 556)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 557)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 558)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, Boston, Revere Beach, & Lynn Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 559)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 560)
      - Boston, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 561)
      - Bourne, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1928 (Box 6:, Folder 562)
      - Bournedale, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 563)
      - Bournedale, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad Station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 564)
      - Bradford, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1960 (Box 6:, Folder 565)
      - Braggville, Massachusetts, railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 566)
      - Braintree, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 567)
      - Braintree, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 568)
      - Braintree, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1960 (Box 6:, Folder 569)
      - Braintree, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 6:, Folder 570)
      - Braintree Heights, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 571)
      - Brayton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 572)
      - Brewster, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 573)
      - Brewster, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 574)
      - Brewster, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1937 (Box 6:, Folder 575)
      - Bridgewater, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1962 (Box 6:, Folder 576)
      - Bridgewater, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 577)
      - Bridgewater, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 578)
      - Bridgewater Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1910 (Box 6:, Folder 579)
      - Broadway, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 580)
      - Brockton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 581)
      - Brockton, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 582)
      - Brockton, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 583)
      - Brookfield, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 584)
      - Brookline, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1933 (Box 6:, Folder 585)
      - Brookline, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1933 (Box 6:, Folder 586)
      - Brookline Hills, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 587)
      - Brookline Village, Massachusetts, Boston Electric Street Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 588)
      - Browns Crossing, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 589)
      - Burrage, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1936 (Box 6:, Folder 590)
      - Buzzards Bay, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 591)
      - Buzzards Bay, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 592)
      - Buzzards Bay, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1963 (Box 6:, Folder 593)
      - Buzzards Bay, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1980 (Box 6:, Folder 594)
      - Buzzards Bay, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 595)
      - Cambridge, Massachusetts, Fitchburg Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 596)
      - Campells, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 597)
      - Camp Station, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1927 (Box 6:, Folder 598)
      - Cannondale, Massachusetts, railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 599)
      - Canton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1939 (Box 6:, Folder 600)
      - Canton Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1965 (Box 6:, Folder 601)
      - Canton Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1938 (Box 6:, Folder 602)
      - Canton Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 603)
      - Canton Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1962 (Box 6:, Folder 604)
      - Carltonville, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad Station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 605)
      - Carters, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 606)
      - Carters, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 6:, Folder 607)
      - Caryville, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1962 (Box 6:, Folder 608)
      - Caryville, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1926 (Box 6:, Folder 609)
      - Caryville, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 610)
      - Castle Hill, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 611)
      - Cataumet, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 6:, Folder 612)
      - Catuamet, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1968 (Box 6:, Folder 613)
      - Cataumet, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1968 (Box 6:, Folder 614)
      - Cedar, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 615)
      - Cedar, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 616)
      - Central Square, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 617)
      - Chace's Station, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1910 (Box 6:, Folder 618)
      - Chaffins, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 6:, Folder 619)
      - Charlemont, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 7:, Folder 620)
      - Charlemont, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1977 (Box 7:, Folder 621)
      - Charlemont, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1977 (Box 7:, Folder 622)
      - Charles River, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1962 (Box 7:, Folder 623)
      - Charles River, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1938 (Box 7:, Folder 624)
      - Charlton, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 625)
      - Chatham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1986 (Box 7:, Folder 626)
      - Chatham Center, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1984 (Box 7:, Folder 627)
      - Chelsea, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 628)
      - Cheshire, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 7:, Folder 629)
      - Chester, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1891 (Box 7:, Folder 630)
      - Chester, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1929 (Box 7:, Folder 631)
      - Chester, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1929 (Box 7:, Folder 632)
      - Chester, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 633)
      - Chesnut Hill, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 634)
      - Chicopee, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad Station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 635)
      - Chicopee Center, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 636)
      - Chicopee Falls, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 637)
      - Chicopee Junction, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 638)
      - Clarendon Hills, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 639)
      - Clarendon Hills, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 640)
      - Cliquot, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 641)
      - Cliquot, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 642)
      - Cliquot, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 643)
      - Cliquot, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1958 (Box 7:, Folder 644)
      - Cliquot, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 7:, Folder 645)
      - Cochesett, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 646)
      - Cochituate, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1933 (Box 7:, Folder 647)
      - Cohasset, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 648)
      - Cohasset, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 649)
      - Coldbrook, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 7:, Folder 650)
      - Collins, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 7:, Folder 651)
      - Collins, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 7:, Folder 652)
      - Collins Street, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 653)
      - Coltsville, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 7:, Folder 654)
      - Concord, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 655)
      - Cordage, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 656)
      - Cordage, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad Station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 657)
      - Cordaville, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 658)
      - Cordaville, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 659)
      - Cottage Farm, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1929 (Box 7:, Folder 660)
      - Cranes, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 661)
      - Creamery, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 662)
      - Crescent Avenue, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 663)
      - Cross Street (Winchester), Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 664)
      - Curtis Crossing, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 665)
      - Dalton, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1977 (Box 7:, Folder 666)
      - Dalton, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1977 (Box 7:, Folder 667)
      - Dalton, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 668)
      - Danvers, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1959 (Box 7:, Folder 669)
      - Danvers, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 670)
      - Danversport, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1963 (Box 7:, Folder 671)
      - Danversport, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1934 (Box 7:, Folder 672)
      - Darby, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1925 (Box 7:, Folder 673)
      - Dawson, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 674)
      - Dean Street, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1906 (Box 7:, Folder 675)
      - Dedham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 676)
      - Dedham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1938 (Box 7:, Folder 677)
      - Dedham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1928 (Box 7:, Folder 678)
      - Dedham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1906 (Box 7:, Folder 679)
      - Deerfield Junction, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 680)
      - Deerfield, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 681)
      - Diamond Hill, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 682)
      - Diamond Hill, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 683)
      - Diamond Hill, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 684)
      - Dodgeville, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 685)
      - Dorchester, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 686)
      - Dover, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1888 (Box 7:, Folder 687)
      - Dunstable, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1911 (Box 7:, Folder 688)
      - Duxbury, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 689)
      - East Boxford, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 690)
      - East Braintree, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 691)
      - East Brewster, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1957 (Box 7:, Folder 692)
      - East Brewster, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 693)
      - East Bridgewater, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 694)
      - East Bridgewater, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 695)
      - East Brimfield, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 7:, Folder 696)
      - East Brookfield, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1969 (Box 7:, Folder 697)
      - East Brookfield, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1969 (Box 7:, Folder 698)
      - East Brookfield, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 699)
      - East Cambridge, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 700)
      - East Dedham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 701)
      - East Dedham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 7:, Folder 702)
      - East Dedham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 703)
      - East Everett, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 704)
      - East Foxboro, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 705)
      - East Foxboro, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 7:, Folder 706)
      - East Freetown, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 707)
      - East Greenbush, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 7:, Folder 708)
      - East Holliston, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 711)
      - East Holliston, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 7:, Folder 712)
      - East Holliston, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1959 (Box 7:, Folder 713)
      - East Holliston, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1961 (Box 7:, Folder 714)
      - East Holliston, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1961 (Box 7:, Folder 715)
      - East Holliston, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 716)
      - East Lexington, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 717)
      - East Longmeadow, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1936 (Box 7:, Folder 718)
      - East Longmeadow, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1967 (Box 7:, Folder 719)
      - East Lynn, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 720)
      - East Lyon, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1918 (Box 7:, Folder 721)
      - East Middleboro, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1912 (Box 7:, Folder 722)
      - East Northfield, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 7:, Folder 723)
      - East Pepperell, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 7:, Folder 726)
      - East Portal, Massachusetts, Fitchburg Railroad station, 1892 (Box 8:, Folder 727)
      - East Sandwich, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 8:, Folder 728)
      - East Saugus, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 8:, Folder 729)
      - East Somerville, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1902 (Box 8:, Folder 730)
      - East Somerville, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 8:, Folder 731)
      - East Springfield, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 8:, Folder 732)
      - East Taunton, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1928 (Box 8:, Folder 733)
      - East Walpole, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1926 (Box 8:, Folder 734)
      - East Walpole, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1910 (Box 8:, Folder 735)